club-xxx.net 2015-12-07

# club-xxx.net

Our Commitment To Privacy:  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.   
To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect:  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on club-xxx.net website. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name:  
Address:  
Email address:  
Phone number:  
Country:  
City:  
Zip code:

The Way We Use Information:  
We request information from the user on our signup form. Here a user must provide contact information (name, email, country, city, phone number). If we have any questions about user account, or some trouble processing his order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. We don't use the information for any secondary purposes. We don't reveal this information to any third parties.

Our Commitment To Data Security:  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information.

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to our members area. This part of our site is located on a secure SSL server, and all information is encrypted with a 128-bit key. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

contacting club-xxx.net,  
Please fill in the enquiry form for your questions  
concerning our privacy policy.
